[{"answer": "I didn't know what to think until I got on the phone and within one minute I thought I was in trouble, because the first thing he said to me was, Dean, I've heard you speak and I've heard you speak about your first program, which is about convincing kids that science and technology is critical to their future.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "And then suddenly, out of nowhere, you get a call from this guy, front man of the Black Eyed Peas, one of the biggest pop stars in the world, music stars, what are you thinking?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "That's a very good shorthand.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Is that the easiest way to describe?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Oh, wholeheartedly.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Do you believe that?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "From England.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "So this amazing outfit you wore at the Super Bowl, which was this all-flashing, all-singing, all-dancing electronic super outfit, in fact the guy that designed the code for this was a graduate of the FIRST, originally, right?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "He makes an appearance on the show.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Does he have any involvement with this now, especially now you've got involved?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "He does?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "On Sunday, August 14th.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "On Sunday?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "No, just applauding and, you know, congratulating the kids and showing support for their discipline and hard work.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Is he playing with a robot or?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "That wasn't a question.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "It's a question with \"Yes, We Can,\" has he?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Interestingly, back in Britain at the moment, we've had a lot of riots this week.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "To do your part to inspire someone to do their part?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "I remember the L.A. riot, the race riots in the early '90s.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "When you see what's going on with these riots and stuff, do you have an empathy with these kids or do you believe that actually the way out is to go another way?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "They are.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "But I know they're part of your twisted mind, aren't they, Dean?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "I love what they do for kids.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "You love these things, don't you?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "This is the showoff entertainer but doesn't do very much, right?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "This robot, you know that robot dance that we do?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "A big kid built that.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "One of the kids built this or a team of kids?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "This is the real brains one, right?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "It was humiliating.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Well, the goal of the robot -- every year we give the kids a different challenge.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "It's not fully functional right now, but what can he do when he's going?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "They're remote-controlled.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "How does it work?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Encouragement.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "What do you think got you out?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "My family, family friends, my teachers, Mr. Wright (ph), Ms. Montez (ph).", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "From who?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "No, but they do have somebody.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "When you see these gang kids, is a big part of the problem the fact they don't have anybody?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "ILL.I.AM: Well, it depends on the people around you.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Can you achieve this kind of thing without the driving force of a mother or a father, somebody who is with you to be able to provide a chance to do it?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Your mother must be pretty proud of you.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "And -- but yes, there's always ways out of it, you know?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "You answered the question yourself.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "How important is it to you to get somebody like him who, in one swoop, can basically get to millions and millions of kids in this country?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "It goes over my head because I can't comprehend it.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "What do you think of America as a business model right now?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "AMEN: I agree, as usual, with Will.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Dean, what do you think?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Progress has always depended on innovation.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Should that be where America leads the field?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "That's a slight exaggeration.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Again, not babysitter.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Was he a good baby sitter?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, yes.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "No, like back flips.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Tom Cruise would be doing cartwheels?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Oh yes, oh yes.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "I do, actually.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Do you still see him?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "I think -- personally, I think a really fortunate thing, because it exposed me to the business that I found myself in as an adult.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Has that been, on balance, a good thing or not a good thing for you?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "I was (INAUDIBLE) --", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "And the reason you're called Dallas is because?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "My sisters are twins.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "And your siblings's middle names are?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "I've immersed myself in your life.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Where do you get all of this information?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Do you ever get tempted?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Ever smoked?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Well, yeah, totally.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Any vices?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Your vice is sugar?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "It was such an incredible thing that happened.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "What do you feel watching it now?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "I haven't really thought about that, I mean, because it was a book first, and because --", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "ORGAN: Are you worried about any controversy that this role will bring you?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "I'm almost five months.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "How many months pregnant are you now?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "It is -- it's amazing.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "How is it all going?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "I mean I do.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "ORGAN: Do you have any worries it may happen again?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Two actors together, with all of the, you know, insecurity that comes with acting, and the egos and all of the rest of it.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "He's doing well, yes.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "The old man's got a few stashed away, hasn't he?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "In his office.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Where does he keep them?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Have you written the speech in your mind?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "Well, here's what would happen --", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Who are you going to thank?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "Yeah, there's a lot of people to be grateful to.", "docId": "110812pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "I mean, what a speech you've got ready to go, huh?", "qSentId": 619}]